English Subtitles.
Two and a Half Men S03E03 - Carpet Burns and a Bite Mark - Web-DL [KoTuWa]
...fifteen-yard line,
where the officials will mark it.
Russell, the quarterback...
Will you please stop that?
I got a piece of popcorn stuck
in my teeth.
- So go brush them.
- I brushed them this morning.
- So go floss them.
- Oh, gross.
Wait. I got it.
No, that's chicken.
When did we have chicken?
You didn't brush this morning,
did you?
Between you and me,
I lost my toothbrush three days ago.
Still good.
Hey, have you met any of the ladies
my dad's been dating?
- No. You?
- No.
More chicken?
Fingernail.
Yours?
I hope so.
So how come I don't get to meet
Dad's dates?
I don't know,
maybe because you're disgusting.
No, come on, really.
I'm not kidding. For most women,
you're a deal breaker.
You used to say I was a babe magnet.
You used to be little and cute.
Now you're just old and in the way.
That's very hurtful, Uncle Charlie.
The truth is your dad doesn't want you
to get attached to these women...
...in case the relationship
doesn't work.
Why?
He loves you very much
and he cares about your feelings.
You let me meet your dates.
And what does that tell you?
I have no idea.
Hello?
Hi, Dad.
What are you doing up so late?
Charlie, what is he doing up?
He's asleep.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Charlie.
- What?
Oh, hey, Alan.
What is he doing up so late?
I told him to go to bed.
How many times did I tell you?
Boy, I lost count.
See?
- So how was your date?
- Lt was fine.
Did you get any?
- Did I get any what?
- Hang on.
What's he supposed to get?
I swear I don't know
what he's talking about.
Go to bed.
- What are you teaching him?
- What difference does it make?
The only thing he retains
is little shards of chicken.
Wonderful.
So did you get any?
A nice evening.
We had a lovely dinner.
For the record, a lovely dinner...
...doesn't necessarily preclude
carpet burns...
...and a bite mark on your ass.
In this case, it was just dinner
and pleasant conversation.
Well, that's why God gave us
Cinemax and an opposable thumb.
Good evening.
Alan, the kid was asking about these
women you've been going out with.
Why he never meets them.
Really? What did you tell him?
I said it's probably
because he's disgusting.
Oh, Charlie...
I also told him that you love him,
you don't want him to get attached...
...be disappointed
if things don't work.
Good. Thank you.
But how come
I don't get to meet them?
Because you're disgusting.
That's very hurtful, Alan.
Come on, really.
What's the big secret
with these women?
Boy, I really don't wanna get into it.
- They're hideous, right?
- No.
- Insufferable? Inflatable?
- Are you insane?
- Insane. Are they insane?
- Leave me alone.
- Come on, give me a hint.
When you go to pick them up...
...do you need a Border collie
to cut them off?
Stop it.
I'm never gonna stop, Alan.
You know me better than that.
Okay, fine. I'll tell you.
First of all, there's no women.
Imaginary. My next guess
was gonna be imaginary.
Let me finish.
It's just one woman.
I've been seeing the same woman
for weeks.
- I see. You've been playing it slow.
- Yes.
And by slow I mean gay.
I can't talk to you about this.
Alan, you hook a fish
and play it too long.
You know what
you have when you reel it in?
- What?
- A tired fish that thinks you're gay.
Do you drink
while you're babysitting my son?
Not at first, but he wears me down.
- So, what's the deal with this broad?
- She's not a broad.
It's Judith.
- Your ex-wife?
- Yep.
Okay, okay. That's not fair.
You said no to insufferable
and insane.
- Very funny.
- Are you serious?
And by serious I mean dumber
than a bag of doorknobs.
Look, we went out
to dinner weeks ago...
...to talk about getting Jake
into middle school.
Before you know it, we're laughing,
having a great time.
I can see the humor in trying to get
the little bonehead into a good school.
But that doesn't mean you start
dating your ex-wife.
I know what you're thinking.
I'm being naive and romantic.
Not even close.
You can't overlook the fact
that we still have a lot in common.
Yeah, neither of you
have any respect for you.
The point is, she wants to give it
another try and so do I.
We can't let Jake know, we don't
want him to get his hopes up.
Oh, buddy, why don't you just take
an electric sander to your testicles?
We're both adults,
we're aware of the pitfalls...
...and we think it's worth the risk.
Okay, fine. I wish you both
nothing but happiness.
Thank you.
Hello.
What's going on?
Sit down, Alan. We need to talk.
Yeah, well, listen, I'd love to but
I've gotta wake up Jake so we can...
Let him sleep.
Am I getting whacked?
It was discussed,
but I was overruled.
Sit down.
Alan, we're all here
because we love you.
And we don't wanna see you
make a terrible mistake.
I'm just waiting
for my toaster strudel to pop.
There we go.
You told on me.
Hey, you wouldn't listen to reason,
so now you're gonna listen to Mom.
Alan, sweetheart, you know,
I only want the best for you, right?
I do.
Which is why when Judith threw
you out, I was there supporting you.
- You had other options?
- Don't be naive.
I could have sucked up to Judith...
...in order to have more access
to my grandson.
But no, I burned that bridge.
I said horrible things to her
that I can never take back.
Keep in mind, this is a woman who
worked the phrase "mousy bitch"...
...into her wedding toast.
So if you two reconcile,
I'll have to apologize to her.
- So?
- I'd rather kill us all.
Okay, moving on.
Rose? Do you have something
you'd like to say?
Yes, thank you.
Alan, when I first met you,
I didn't care for you at all.
You were a fussy, whiny control freak.
Yes? And now?
Now it doesn't bother me so much.
I think what Rose means is that
since the divorce, you've grown...
...you've been reborn.
That's not what I meant.
If that was what I meant,
that's what I would've said.
- Sorry.
- Yeah, you'll get your turn.
Okay.
Alan, life is all about moving on.
Now, in the animal kingdom,
sharks move forward...
...while crabs move sideways.
So the question you have to ask
yourself is:
Are you a shark or a crab?
Which way do Sea-Monkeys move?
Okay, that's Judith.
Now, I thank you for your concern...
...but I would appreciate it
if nobody said anything...
...and everybody just stayed out of it.
Yeah, right.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hi, honey. Why aren't you dressed?
I told you I was picking him up early.
Why isn't he ready? Get dressed.
- I'm sorry.
- You're always sorry...
...but I always play the bad guy.
- Damn it, Alan.
- Okay, he's gone.
- I was thinking about you last night.
- Really?
- What were you thinking?
- Just what a nice time I had.
Yes, yes, it was.
Alan?
Turn around.
Hi, Judith.
Hello. How are you?
Fine.
Bye, Dad. Bye, everybody.
Bye, Jake.
- Goodbye.
- Thanks for staying out of it.
- You're welcome.
Hey, Alan. Come on out,
I got a surprise for you.
Can it wait? Jake forgot
his math book. I'll run it to Judith's.
No, no, no.
You can't go to Judith's.
The surprise is ready now.
Okay. What is it?
Oh, for God's sake.
Wait, there's more.
Twins, Alan. I got them for you,
but you can share if you want.
Charlie, no.
Fine, you can have them both.
Bad luck to split sisters anyway.
I don't want them.
I'm going to Judith's.
I don't think you're getting
the full picture.
Turn around.
Show him the full picture.
That's daily Pilates classes
and one meal a month.
- I'll see you later.
- Are you sure?
Even together, these girls aren't
as old as your ex-wife.
Bye.
Oh, for the love of God.
Stop turning.
Show's over.
- Isn't he adorable?
- Yeah.
When he's sleeping,
he's like a little angel.
I was planning to have
a glass of wine...
...sit in the hot tub
before you came.
I'm sorry. I just wanted to be sure
he got the book. I'll get out.
Alan. Would you like to join me?
Well, I didn't bring a bathing suit.
You don't need a bathing suit.
Okay.
Have you been keeping up
the chlorine treatments?
Without a bathing suit, you're just
inviting algae into your privates.
- I like the new patio furniture.
- Thanks.
- What is that, redwood?
- Teak.
Oh, teak. That must have set me
back a few bucks.
The salesman said it would pay
for itself in five years.
Oh, really? How is it gonna do that?
Is it gonna get a paper route?
- It's very nice.
- Thank you.
Of course, it's gonna require a lot
of upkeep.
Actually, all wood that's outside
requires upkeep except trees.
They seem to have it down.
Alan, are you nervous?
Yeah, a little.
I mean, we've been separated
for two years.
I haven't seen you naked for four.
Except, you know, that one time
I walked in on you on the toilet.
Mom? You out there?
Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
- Take a deep breath.
- What?
I'm thirsty.
- Have something to drink.
- There's no more Goofy Juice.
- So have some water.
- Fine.
- Hey, Mom?
- What?
I'm hungry too.
Can you make me a sandwich?
- No. Have your drink and go to bed.
- Fine.
Mom.
- How about a cookie?
- You already brushed your teeth.
- No, I didn't.
- You said you did.
I always say that.
- Well, then brush them and go to bed.
- Fine.
Oh, God.
Are you okay?
There was a bright light
and I saw my dead grandma.
She seemed happy.
Here, have a little wine.
Thank you. Thank you.
That was close.
Relax, he didn't see you.
But what if he comes back?
Maybe I should go.
Or we could go upstairs
and get in bed.
Bed?
- Our old bed?
- My new bed.
Oh, what was wrong
with the old one?
- Too many memories.
- Of what?
You pretending to sleep
and me watching Letterman?
Alan, do you wanna have this
conversation?
No, I don't. But apparently,
my mouth has a mind of its own.
Well, let's put your mouth
to better use.
I can't go back underwater, Judith.
- Hey, Charlie.
- Yeah?
Not that it's any of my business...
...I couldn't help noticing
the matched set...
...of rotating floozies
on your deck earlier.
They were for Alan. I was trying
to get his mind off of Judith.
With a night of meaningless,
impersonal group sex?
What a good brother.
No, no, a good brother
gets him a couple of girls.
It takes a great brother
to get him two from the same egg.
You know, there is a possibility
that we were wrong about this.
Maybe Alan and Judith
can work things out.
Maybe. But if they do...
- ...what happens to Jake?
- Grows up in a happy home...
...with a mommy and daddy
who love each other?
Yeah, but what about me?
It's too late for you, Charlie.
No, I mean,
what happens to me and Jake?
I'll never get to see him.
You really love the little guy, huh?
Yeah, I guess I do.
Love hurts, Rose.
Yes, it does.
Especially when you've given
your heart...
...to someone who barely knows
you exist.
Who insists on plowing through
strange, stupid women...
...who could never love him
the way you do...
...leaving you to stand outside...
...alone in the night...
...wishing with all your heart
that he would come to his senses...
...and realize that his true happiness
lies with you and no one else...
...but knowing all the while
that it will never happen...
...because he's a selfish, immature,
heartless jerk.
I mean...
...poor baby.
Okay, I'm gonna stick my neck
out here...
...and say that was the best sex
we ever had.
- I agree.
- Not that it wasn't good before.
It wasn't.
Okay, granted.
Which raises the question:
Why is it so much better now?
- Does it matter?
- Well, no, not really.
I mean, just curious.
I mean, I...
I noticed some new moves
on your part...
...and I can't help wondering where
you might have picked them up.
You haven't been with other women
in two years?
Oh, no, I've been with other women,
I just didn't learn anything.
You, on the other hand, have
an entirely new sexual repertoire...
...including a couple of numbers
I requested when we were married.
- Alan...
- And by requested I mean begged.
Please don't go there.
Now, see, that's what I'm used to
hearing from you in bed.
"Don't go there. " "Don't touch that."
"Leave that alone, it's not a toy."
So I've changed.
I would think you would be happy.
Well, I was. Very happy.
But then I started to think about it.
There's no reason
you couldn't have changed with me.
- Oh, please.
- I gave you every chance.
I bought tickets to sex seminars,
I brought home books...
...and tapes and accessories.
And what happened?
I sat right here reading
and watching by myself...
...while eating low-fat love jelly
out of the tube.
Okay, I can see this was a bad idea.
No, the bad idea was sitting in
that filthy hot tub...
...without a bathing suit.
I can feel mushrooms
growing in my crack.
Just go home, Alan.
We're not married.
You can't tell me what to do.
- Hey, Mom? Does this look infected?
- Okay, bye!
It's okay, I didn't see anything.
Hey.
What are you watching?
Soft-core porn.
Sound's not on.
I don't need to hear them.
Aren't those the twins
from the deck?
Too late now, Alan.
You could have been delivering
that pizza.
How's Judith?
Fine.
She got some new patio furniture.
That's nice.
Teak.
Put in some rose bushes too.
How about that.
And I think the neighbors
got a new dog.
Mean dog.
Really?
Might have been a coyote.
Hard to say.
It was dark and I was crying.
- Anything else?
- No.
Oh, yeah,
I saw our dead grandmother.
- Where?
- Ln the hot tub.
Oh, that's the cab.
Could you lend me 60 bucks?
I don't have my wallet on me.
Sure.
Oh, thank you.
I suddenly have a craving
for pizza.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]