English Subtitles.
Two and a Half Men S03E23 - Arguments for the Quickie - Web-DL [KoTuWa]
- Morning.
Yeah, what's up?
Oh, stop it.
- Hey. Give me back my skully.
- This is not a skully.
It's a ski cap your grandmother
gave you for Christmas.
- Charlie, he's just trying to find his look.
- Word.
Word?
There's a reindeer on it.
Don't listen to him, Jake.
I think it looks very dope on you.
Oh, man.
Oh, hey, did you see that your former
girlfriend's dance troupe is in town?
Mia's here? Let me see that.
Come on, come on, come on.
Whoa, is somebody
still carrying a torch?
Torch? Don't be ridiculous.
I mean, I'm glad to see she's following
her dream but I've moved on.
- I think she called the other day.
- What? When?
What did she want?
What did she say?
Come on, kid, spill it.
Nope, no unresolved feelings there.
She wanted to talk to you
but you weren't home.
I know that, you chowderhead.
What else did she say?
She said, "What's new?"
I said, "Nothing much."
And then she said, "How's school?"
I said, "it sucks."
Then she said, "That's too bad."
I said, "Yeah."
I'm gonna kill him, Alan.
I swear to God I'm gonna kill him.
Oh, yeah, she wants us
to come see her dance next weekend.
It says she's performing this weekend.
Oh, I guess she called last weekend.
- You're telling me this now?
- Charlie. Calm down.
How many things
does the kid have to handle?
Eat, poop, tell me who called.
She said some guy named Will
has tickets.
- Who's Will?
- I don't know. She said he'd call.
Will's gonna call?
- You mean the tickets are at will call?
- I don't know. Maybe.
Dear God, he's a doorstop that eats.
Do me a favor. From now on,
when somebody calls, write it down.
- I did.
- Where?
- On my homework.
- Okay, where's your homework?
Oh yeah, my teacher called.
She wants to meet with you.
When?
Oh, I guess it was last week.
Peace out.
Great. Great. Thank you.
Mia left us four seats for Friday night.
House seats, center orchestra.
What do you think? You, me, Jake, Kandi,
go out to dinner, make an evening of it?
Sounds like fun.
Maybe afterwards you could tie me to an
anthill, and smear honey on my genitals.
So you don't wanna go?
Jeez, now I see where
the kid gets his brains.
No, I don't wanna go.
Why would I wanna go?
Because you were in love
with the woman...
...and still have feelings for her
and wanna see her.
Oh, that's crazy.
God, you are so naive.
- How am I naive?
- Oh, oh, I know this one.
Alan, when an ex-girlfriend calls,
no good can come from it.
Unless, you know,
it's 2 a.m., she's blind drunk...
...and wants to get even
with her new cheating boyfriend.
She just wanted to invite us
to the ballet.
Yeah, right.
And girls are completely unaware...
...that you can see their nipples
through their shirts.
What does that have to...?
Really, they know?
There's only a few reasons
why an ex calls.
One, they're great,
and wanna rub your nose in it.
Or two, they're doing lousy
and need to borrow money.
Three, they got money
from knocking over a Laundromat...
...and wanna hide it under your trailer
until the heat's off.
It happens.
Okay, okay, how about four?
She misses you, and wants to try again?
What is it she's gonna try?
To change me into something I'm not?
To get me to stop drinking,
smoking, gambling?
To rescue me from the barren,
loveless abyss my life has become?
What?
You know what I think?
You were never happier
than when you were with Mia.
You still have feelings for her.
You're afraid to admit it.
You are so wrong.
You couldn't be more wrong.
- You believe that guy?
- You want the truth?
- No, probably not.
- Good call.
Oh, by the way,
here's the 20 bucks I owe you.
I am telling you, it is not appropriate
to wear to the ballet.
Why you tripping on me?
Hey, Alan. Matey.
- I'm not a pirate.
- You're not a gangsta either.
You're a dorky, white kid
with a Cub Scout bandana on his head.
Yo, hate the game,
don't hate the player.
You know kids better than me.
How long does this pimp stage last?
Just ignore him.
- You sure you won't come with us?
- Positive.
- Should I at least say hi to Mia for you?
- Say what you want.
- I'm meeting somebody at Pavlov's.
- Who?
How would I know?
I haven't met her yet.
Hi. Do I look okay?
- Perfect.
- Hey, no fair.
You grow a rack like that, you can
wear anything you want on your head.
You have a house on the beach?
I'd love to see it.
- I could take you there.
- Great.
Then I could bring you out
on my deck.
We could watch the surf
in the moonlight.
Then I could take you in my arms,
kiss you. Not a big kiss.
Just a little something that gives you
a taste of what's to come.
Well, let's go.
I'd take your hand
and lead you up to my bedroom...
...where I'd slowly undress you.
Then lay you down on the crisp,
cool sheets...
...and make wild, passionate love
to you until we're both totally spent.
Okay.
Then in the morning, I'll bring you
a cup of coffee and your car keys.
Wait, my car keys?
I'll promise to call you
but I never will.
And when you call me, you'll find
that the phone number I gave you...
...belongs to a dry cleaner
in Korea-town.
What?
When all is said and done,
you know what we'll both have?
Nothing.
Not even a good memory.
What do you say we do us both a favor
and not go through with this charade?
Okay.
Jeez, I was just trying to get laid.
See, Jake, the swan is dying.
Can you believe...?
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Pardon me. Excuse me. Hey.
- What did I miss?
- I thought you weren't coming.
I'm not here for Mia.
I'm here to support the arts.
Yikes, look at the package
on that pretty dude.
Hey, good job.
Eat something.
- Charlie.
- Hey. You were terrific.
Thank you.
- I'm so glad you came.
- Are you kidding me?
I've been looking forward to this
all week.
- Dressed like that?
- Well, how else would you recognize me?
- These are for you.
- Thank you. They're beautiful.
No big deal, they had them
at the liquor store.
It was either this
or a stack of lotto scratchers.
- I think you made the wise choice.
- We'll never know, will we?
Alan would've come,
but he had to take the kids home.
- Kids?
- He's kind of adopted a young girl.
- Really?
- Well, not so much adopted as banging.
So you're looking good.
- You too. How have you been?
- Great. Just great. Really great.
- Good.
- No, no. No, great.
- And you, how have you been?
- Wonderful.
All right then, I'm great
and you're wonderful.
So what the hell are we doing here?
There was something
I wanted to talk to you about.
- Hey, Mia. Who's your cute friend?
- This is Charlie. Charlie, Theresa.
Hey.
So, what did you want
to talk to me about?
This really isn't the right place.
Why don't I get changed
and stop by your house?
Sure. I'll be up.
- Because, you know, I'm a night person.
- I remember.
Of course, if you come too late,
I could be drunk.
- I remember.
- There could be other women there.
I remember.
- See you later.
- Whatever.
Hey, can you unhook me?
What's going on?
Nothing.
Mia's coming over, so I thought I'd...
- I see.
- What do you mean you see?
You're right. It's too much.
- How's that?
- Well, I...
Right. She'll smell there were candles
burning, so I have to light at least one.
- What about the music?
- What about it?
You're right.
Sounds like I'm trying too hard.
- Better?
- Well, I...
You're right.
No music.
- Charlie?
- Yeah?
I'm just glad you're over her.
Get the door. Get the door.
Get the door.
- Hi, Alan.
- Hey, Mia, you were great tonight.
- Thanks. Did Jake like it?
- He was absolutely knocked out.
Charlie, Mia's here.
Oh, really?
- Well, ask her in.
- All right.
- Won't you come in?
- Okay.
Hi, Mia, I almost forgot
you were coming.
Get out.
- Nice to see you again.
- Nice to see you too.
Sit down, make yourself at home.
Place looks the same.
Well, you know me,
if it ain't broke, don't fix it.
If it is broke, who gives a rat's ass?
- Can I get you a drink?
- No, I'm good.
- So am I. In fact, I'm great.
- Yeah, you mentioned that.
Repeatedly.
So, what did you wanna talk about?
Oh, boy.
This is a hard thing to ask.
You need some money.
What? No.
So, what? You wanna get back
together again?
Oh, God no.
All right, then, how about
a quickie for old times' sake?
Please.
Charlie...
...I think you're a terrific guy.
You're smart, you're handsome,
you're talented.
All good arguments for the quickie.
- Will you let me finish?
- Didn't I always?
Sorry. Sorry, go on.
I've been thinking a lot lately
about what I want out of life.
I love dancing, but let's face it,
I'm not getting any younger.
So the time has come
for me to make some tough choices.
- I understand completely.
- You do?
No, I'm just trying to be supportive.
Charlie, I came here because...
Well...
I want your sperm.
All right, where do you want it?
- Alan, Alan, wake up. Wake up.
- What?
Mia wants sperm.
Well, don't look at me.
No, no, she wants my sperm.
She wants me to make a deposit
so she can have a baby.
- You're kidding.
- Apparently, that's another of its uses.
What the hell is that?
I'm not sure. Near as I can tell,
she's chasing a rabbit.
So why did Mia come to you?
Well, it turns out
her biological clock is ticking.
Most of the guys she meets are
ballet dancers, so, slim pickings there.
She doesn't wanna wait
for Mr. Right to come along.
- Which pretty much leaves you.
- Yep.
I'm good genetic material,
you know, easy on the eyes.
And she wants to raise the kid alone
which fits nicely into my lifestyle.
Charlie, drinking, gambling
and casual sex is not a lifestyle.
Okay, okay, I didn't come in here
to argue with you.
Look in the hedges,
look in the hedges.
What?
I don't know.
So, what are you gonna do?
You gonna go to a sperm bank?
Well, I tried to talk her into
a direct deposit.
You know, straight from the tap.
But she really dug in her heels.
And not in the good way.
- And you're okay with it?
- Well, why not?
I've sent billions of soldiers out there.
It's time for one of them
to finally take the hill.
- Now what?
- I think she caught the rabbit.
Anyway, I'm thinking
this could be my one chance...
...to guarantee
that the Charlie gene lives on.
You know, make sure
the double helix that is uniquely me...
...keeps on trucking into the future.
Okay, let's assume
that's a good thing.
- One more question.
- Yeah?
If you have no doubts,
why'd you wake me up to tell me?
Well, you're my brother...
...and I thought you should know
you're gonna be an uncle.
You mean, I'm gonna be an uncle
to a child I'll never see.
Tell you what, when he turns 12,
I'll track him down...
...bring him to live with you and we'll
see if you get your phone messages.
- What do you think?
- Looks like pretty standard boilerplate.
It says that once your swim team's
off the bus, you're no longer the coach.
All right. Let's see, where do I sign?
The old John Hancock, if you will.
You sure you want to?
You're giving up the rights
not only to your sperm...
...but to any children
that might result from them. It.
- I understand.
- Do you?
Once you sign, Mia can do whatever
she wants with it. Them.
She can use it, resell it, freeze it,
put it on eBay.
Hey, I don't care if she uses it
to caulk her bathtub.
Once the boys reach escape velocity,
they're on their own.
- I see.
- It's out of my hands, so to speak.
I got it.
Okay. I'll be back in two shakes.
Three, if it's cold in there.
Charlie? You okay?
- Charlie?
- What?
You've been in there a long time.
How's it going?
How do you think it's going?
Well, I don't know if this'll help,
but sometimes when I was married...
...I used to pretend I was having sex
with a completely different woman.
Oh, thanks. The image of you
bumping uglies with your ex-wife...
...should really move things along.
Excuse me, I was just trying to help.
Yeah, well, I was just trying
to have sex with a cup.
Don't think of it as a cup.
Think of it as a polyurethane lapdancer.
- Get out.
- I'm going.
- Hello?
- Charlie, I was just getting packed.
Oh, right, you're heading
to San Francisco.
That's gotta be a big ballet town.
Yeah.
So did you go to the sperm bank?
And?
Not a lot of laughs in that place.
I asked the receptionist
if she takes work home with her.
Nothing. Not even a smile.
Thanks for doing this.
You have no idea what it means to me.
Yeah, well, funny thing, turns out
it means something to me too.
- What are you talking about?
- I tried, Mia, I really did.
I tried the magazines, the movies.
You can't imagine
how bad porn acting is...
...until you actually watch more
than three, four minutes at a time.
So you're saying you couldn't? You?
Yeah, I know. What are the odds?
Well, I guess these things happen.
You'll try again. I'm sure you'll do fine.
I don't think so.
Why not?
I have thoughts about the reason...
...things didn't go down
as planned, or actually, up.
Okay, I'm listening.
As I was sitting
in that little sperm cubicle...
...watching Assmasters 7:
The Final Chapter...
...all I could think about was some kid
of mine growing up somewhere...
...and me not having a chance to,
you know, be a part of his life.
- I thought you were okay with that.
- I thought I was too.
But as it turns out, I'm not.
So if this is something
you really wanna do...
...then you're gonna have
to find someone else.
I see.
And by the way, Assmasters 7
is not the final chapter.
They left a lot of loose ends.
All right, well, I gotta go.
- I appreciate the effort.
- Oh, thanks.
I think I have a rotator cuff injury.
Good seeing you again, Charlie.
Good seeing you too.
- Hey, let me float another idea by you.
- What?
It's a little crazy, a little unorthodox.
If you really want a kid,
this could be the solution.
- Charlie, I am not having sex with you.
- Who said anything about having sex?
I'm asking you to marry me.
There's no Charlie here.
Why you stupid girls keep calling?
No, listen, I don't take message.
I do dry cleaning.
One more time,
there's no Charlie here.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]